VALENTINE KIMANI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Atlanta, GA 30350

Phone: 762-448-4346 | Email: valkimani3@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/val-kimani-304a4837/

https://github.com/Valkimani|

SUMMARY

Customer Support Manager at Cinc with experience in troubleshooting and customer service. Effective at combining problem-solving and attention to detail to help improve functionality and customer satisfaction. Proficient troubleshooter, Vast technical Knowledge of the CRM, Collaborative, Organized, Conflict resolution, Time management, Data entry, Teamwork.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript | HTML | React | Node | Express | CSS | Git/GitHub | Heroku | REST API | MySQL | Sequelize | MongoDB | Mongoose | JQuery | Bootstrap | Materialize | Responsive Design

EDUCATION

Georgia Tech University Coding Boot Camp

Atlanta Ga, August- February 2021 Full stack web development

Georgia State University

Atlanta Ga, June 2015- May 2016 Masters in Global Hotel Management

PROJECTS

Subscription Manager

URL: https://boiling-journey-74144.herokuapp.com
Technology: MERN Stack, JSON Web Token, Bycrypt

My Role: Came up with the idea. Design and layout. Full-stack development for

login, signup and subscriptions pages.

Description: Sub Manny is a website that notifies a user when their subscription services raise the plan pricing. The user can add and delete a subscription from a list provided by the Admin.

The Reserve

URL: https://still-ravine-68015.herokuapp.com

Technology: MongoDB, Handlebars, MySql, Sequelize

My Role: Design and layout. Updated the Front-end. Added styling. Utilized

sweetAlert2 for the modules.

Description: The Reserve is a room reservation app that allows college campus library managers to create a log of study rooms. In doing so, it's easier for the manager to keep track of which rooms are in use, empty, or in need of cleaning.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CINC

Atlanta, GA 2018 to current

Title: Customer Support Manager

Description: Provide complex technical support, troubleshooting and assist clients via email and phone while responding to customer inquiries about the platform products and services. Provide customers with configuration recommendations to improve platform usability, performance, and customer satisfaction.

Hyatt Regency

Atlanta, GA 2017 to 2018

Title: Food and Beverage Manger Intern

Description: Assisted managers run the restaurants while responding to customer needs proactively to all their concerns. Utilized computer software programs (MS Office, restaurant management software, POS) to generate sales results and productivity results daily. Delegated tasks to servers and solved conflict.

CERTIFICATIONS

Georgia Tech University Coding Boot camp: Full Stack Web Development SheCodes Coding workshop: HTML, CSS & JS certification

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

Latin dancing, Yoga, Rock climbing, volunteering